Caio is selling cheve eh son,
it's selling cool huh?
day 59
okay
filming,
you saw,
saying you will rotate the bag.
this one is a Chevette,
eighty-six,
s.
l.
and alcohol one point six.
I put all the parts
new ones that were missing now in the chevas,
only the bank here I'm going to have fixed
on my own.
revised engine,
car is complete.
for you who are interested,
glue here high post
Anchieta closed.
it took bro.
in the life of the entrepreneur,
if you want to get somewhere,
there is no way to do this without sacrifice.
for me it is too difficult to get rid of the chevas,
but undertake is that.
is you give up your time,
give up your family,
give up your stuff.
sometimes it's not the decision we would like,
but it is a decision that needs to be made.
oh, Cayon,
suddenly sells the chevas,
things go wrong.
I'll just know if this works out
if I put into practice what you are going to do.
It's a very risk.
do you believe your idea?
the level is low,
is it medium or is it high?
this is the point of analysis.
if I really believe my idea,
no problem
take all my chips and put it in it.
if you are undertaking and not sacrificing yourself,
don't be your time,
family,
friends giving up
to buy something
or selling something to invest in your idea,
I guarantee you my brother,
that.
You're on the wrong track.
as hard as I am selling the chevas,
man,
thirty-one days left for me to open my business
and I realized
that I'm going to need more money than I imagined.
i need to do this,
.